hello my name is green and welcome to
possibly the dullest start to a
hermitcraft you will ever ever encounter
because what I've been doing is not fun
it's not entertaining but I'm gonna take
you through it anyway because it's
important what I've got here are my
shulker boxes that I have crafted that's
right I spent pretty much an entire
afternoon hours and hours
crafting stuff up for Sahara so I've
delivered bone blocks I've got iron
blocks and then this is the chest that
singularly took hours Redstone
comparators repeaters and observers all
of this stuff is going to be sold at
Sahara and it is just about ready for
delivery boy oh boy not very exciting
I'm afraid now we don't really have a
loading area so what I'm gonna do is
just pop all of this stuff down
straight on here now that might be
probably the most boring start to an
episode but this is a pretty big deal
because all of these represent huge
amounts of diamonds for us as a shop but
all of that stock means absolutely
nothing if nobody wants to shop at
Sahara so I have a few ideas on how to
get people shopping at Sahara so
hopefully we can get this place stocked
up
but first I think what we should do is a
little bit of marketing for the shop
itself this pig represents exactly how I
felt trying to craft everything it drove
me a bit insane one of the things that I
did in my last marketing campaign was a
bit of a tester and I did a leaflet drop
now we're gonna do that again but we're
gonna try and get as many Hermits as we
can and see if this works at all I know
exactly where my paper ended up so I
won't even have to craft them all again
and
don't worry guys I'm a professional
Minecrafter I believe we are in iskau's
base it is right here these are all the
ones that I dropped on stress monster so
all I'm gonna do is take these back and
we can get Ren and Scar today so that's
definitely what we're gonna do okay so
what we need to do is get rid of all of
our items literally everything we do not
need I am currently stocked up with
paper and I actually forgot some of
these These are actually pretty funny a
coupon for one sale at Sahara one sale
is one smile
and then I get increasingly desperate
please papers something to do with
Sahara
completely forgot about these
Tara needs customers I think that one's
my favorite coupon for one sale at
Sahara I need to show you guys something
though it's something I discovered when
I was messing around the other day if
you drink a potion of slow falling while
you're flying you guys might know this
but you pretty much just fly really
slowly but if you get it just right you
basically stop like like Frozen in
mid-air
I hit it
looks like the game is completely Frozen
I didn't even mean to do it like this
this is an accident if I look down I do
start falling but look that's the thing
it's quite hard to do you have to twist
yourself around at just the right angle
to stop yourself completely like that
and then you just fall very very slowly
so what I thought we could do for a
start is go and find some of our fellow
Hermits well I say felon Hermits there's
only Scar and rent on at the moment so
we need to go and find them ah scar is
in Cherry at the moment looks like he's
doing some restocking oh my goodness if
if I can do this correctly if I can just
fly in really really well I might be
able to freeze
just in the right spot
he's not
[Laughter]
I don't know my way he was so confused
and now we've got his attention we need
to do the drop oh no oh no it didn't
work oh okay I've got I've only got two
hearts left now we could do the leaflet
drop I need to not miss so hold on let's
go into first person here we go
right where is he he's around there we
go shopping Sahara
there we go there's one leaflet drop
done I've lost my slow falling effect so
now we need to load up again there's one
that says we aren't even open yet but we
definitely are so I've I've actually out
of elytra so I've got to use another one
I can just use a spare one that I've got
but this this will run out very quickly
indeed okay so now we're on the hunt for
Rendog and we're definitely gonna do the
potion of slow falling again oh there it
is that is dojo so he should just see me
flying around if I try and get his
attention the slow falling potion isn't
Gonna Last Forever and I've totally lost
Ren
how is that even possible
there he is there he is he's flying he's
flying he's flying right so now we need
to get his attention in the same way
I've only got nine Rockets left so got
to be careful
and then
yes nailed it now the problem with this
is that I can't actually look down I
don't think he's seen
he's not even here
oh this is awkward oh he's there
you see me
ha
right he seen me I've got I'm gonna get
his attention now now this is falling in
style but where is Ren he's there right
now he's now we've got his undivided
attention so if I get this right it
should go up into one
and now we got it
yes
nailed it hahaha
this is the best leaflet campaign that
has ever been made and it costs
a lot a lot of elyters in order to do
this I hope that they actually return
these green are you okay my dude I was
falling and you know what got me back up
shopping at Sahara
I'm gonna have a lot of fun with this
I am gonna go in I I am gonna need to go
and get my stuff back though I totally
forgot I needed to show you guys this
I've got three stacks of diamonds and
then even more than that I've got more
than three and a half stacks of diamonds
I was running seriously low on funds and
the reason that I now have this many
diamonds is because I managed to sell
another did you die box I upgraded these
to um all God Armor and I managed to
sell the best one for three stacks of
diamonds brilliant I filled up my
inventory with some more promotional
materials and the only person online is
X I zoom R so we're gonna go find him
and see if we can give him some reasons
to shop at Sahara there he is at his
farm oh oh
now how do you get down there so where
is he he's right there aha we're in some
sort of abandoned mine shaft here hold
on let's just uh break in oh he's AFK oh
he's not even here
well there's no need to do a a proper
leaflet drop here he hasn't even got is
this all his stuff he doesn't even oh
well well this just makes it all the
easier all we gotta do is throw all of
the pamphlets down and there they all go
now when he logs back in he's gonna find
himself full of some promotional
material that was the easiest leaflet
drop I've ever done
so now that I've done the leaflet
campaign I need to move on to my next
marketing scheme and that is actually to
make an advert for Sahara we need some
premium ad space but we don't actually
have anything filmed to do it the issue
is I can't do this by myself I actually
need an actor so I have asked Ren the
dog to help me out with that so I'm
gonna go meet up with him now and
discuss this advert that we need to
create what on Earth are you doing
hey Gee I'm training
okay
that I discussed earlier is I want to
make an advert for Sahara because you
know we need more customers we haven't
actually had that many but I'm thinking
a good marketing campaign and it will
all go through the roof so but I can't
actually make it by myself so I actually
need an actor and I mean your sunglasses
and suspenders tells me everything I
need to know about your acting skills
yep yep a class actor right here so I'm
thinking if you help me make this uh
commercial or this advert then I can pay
you at the end and then hopefully get
some sales at Sahara what do you think
uh that sounds like a plan I'm gonna
make some diamonds yeah let's do this
baby so I got I got it I got a script
right here for you so okay they're your
lines
right that that's your bread and butter
you know what you know what to do with
that yeah yeah can I get a moment to
rehearse really quickly that's okay
cool
I mean it just says script on the piece
of paper though
all right let's make this let's make
this thing okay let's do it so Ren and I
did actually spend an hour making an
advert or a commercial if you're from
the states so watch this
hmm man this is expensive I wish there
was a shop that did this all for me at a
competitive price
there is
you gonna pay for that dude no you
should check out Sahara it's a new shop
that does everything for you hmm it
sounds too good to be true why should I
believe you you don't have to just take
it from one of our customers you know
Heroes need exciting products too where
do you think I get all my eggs from
Sahara
um Sahara doesn't sell eggs exactly
because I bought them all but it didn't
even how did you poultry man out
remember we speak Nothing But The Truth
Shop at Sahara and you will live for a
thousand years all right sweet I'll
check it out terms and conditions apply
you will probably not live for a
thousand years
green welcome back to the dojo looks
like you've stolen mumbo's suit uh on
top of that
uh don't eat well Mumbo is now running
around in his underwear I'm just
borrowing his suit okay the dry cleaners
so just boring Mumbo suit doesn't fit
you know he's much more muscly than yeah
don't don't tell him I've been wearing
his clothes please
anyway that that came out really really
good and then now I just need to
distribute that but yeah thank you thank
you so much no I mean that was super fun
this script useless but uh what do you
mean I had a great time it was awesome
however that was quite a lot of work you
know I I could have been training for
the afternoon and instead I made an
advert so cough up my dude all right
yeah yeah yeah maybe some uh give me
some payment yeah yeah that's all sorted
uh there you go there's one right here
for you uh
right I'll be off then
um good day that does that does not
shine green goodbye come back here dude
you know I think I might just wear
mumbo's clothes for the rest of the
episode I feel really Swish and I've got
to say this is probably the only way do
you think people will take me more
seriously if I wear a suit they got to
right they I mean people don't take
Mumbo seriously
dang nabbit either way I wanted to show
you guys my new potato because I have
got my villagers back thankfully after
the entity Purge and they have started
farming carrots again the only problem
is it's now about 50 times slower than
it used to be so they may be farming
away but only during the working hours
of the day and only when they feel like
it I've got to say
it hasn't been great I've got two stacks
of carrots which is pretty bad
especially when you look at this this is
the slowest farm that I had before this
would fill up way quicker than this so
you can see just the comparison of
pumpkins to carrot ratio is it's not
great so what I have done and I've spent
a little bit of time doing I'm
definitely trying to fly without putting
my elytra on how are people gonna take
me seriously if I if I don't play this
game like mumbo jumbo if I'm gonna if
I'm gonna wear mumbo's clothes then I've
got to at least act like Mumbo a little
bit right I've already failed because
this is a manual farm
so what I am gonna do here is I'm gonna
make this is a temporary Farm it's it's
quite big actually this will provide me
with many many carrots and I've just
hidden it right next to Sahara the idea
being that loads of people that work
here whether it's me escout or Mumbo
will all be about and then the carrots
will be uh growing while people are
working
this may take a little while especially
as I don't actually have enough carrots
to start this whole thing off all I have
to do is come and harvest it every now
and again and replant it so it's only a
few minutes work
and I expect that this will produce a
lot more carrots than my automatic farm
will seeing as automatic potato and
carrot Farmers just don't seem to work
very fast
I've got to admit this isn't the funnest
thing that I've done all day and I'm
afraid that's me out of carrots seeing
as that was quite a lot of stacks this
is going to produce more than enough
carrots for the golden carrots for
Sahara it was a bit of a boring task but
to be honest with you it kind of had to
be done either way that's squared away
now we can go back to hermitville where
I really really need to finish working
on my house I wish there was a better
way back to hermitville because at the
moment we have to fly up here fly
through this long tunnel maybe there is
a better way and I just don't know about
it but you have to fly all the way
through here which is a really long way
turn right when you hit the ice and then
you can either follow it down there or
fly through the nether here flight up
here and then into the portal
it's a really quite a long way to travel
between the two it's actually been a
while since I've visited hermitville so
I'm curious to see what damage has been
done
does my house nope my house seems to be
a okay
oh
[Laughter]
my house might be okay
but it looks like looks like the big
plant thing
I'm not really sure what to say
it looks like scar oh okay right so let
me digest this for a second
what we did in our last episode was we
built our house taller and we reflected
the laser beam which then iskal
reflected over back at the plant which
knocked off its eyeball which ended up
down there and it's still there so it's
clearly grown back it's eyeball so now
somehow
because scar
you've turned into a wizard you're a
wizard scar
my Hagrid impression isn't the best okay
but it's a wizard the plant is a wizard
now it's got a giant hat it's got
glasses on
and it's used as spell to stop the laser
beam in its tracks well that's kind of
good because if he didn't the laser beam
would have probably continued forever
but now I believe
yeah that that's probably higher isn't
it the top of this hat
is now taller than my oh maybe it's not
oh we got to do some number crunching
this is 219. yeah it's it's it's three
blocks taller it's three blocks taller
oh man that really sucks
scar you've outdone me again but not for
much longer okay so here's the plan guys
for this episode I don't actually have
enough time to retaliate to this and I
need to think of how I'm going to do my
idea I have probably the most insane
idea
that I've ever come up with for this
build off thing okay it's it's really
gonna well let's just say it's gonna
contest this for sure
the only thing is I don't have enough
time to do it right now so what I'm
going to do is I'm going to spend a
little bit of time finishing off the
decoration for this part of the house
because it's still a bit plain and it
needs doing meaning I'm gonna let scar
have the tallest build
just for an episode but you wait in the
next episode right at the start we're
gonna do something that nobody is
expecting I promise but for now let's
yeah let's just fix this up a little bit
now we haven't actually got that much
work to do seeing as last time I only
had to build up the house a little bit
and I'm not actually going to be working
on anything extra for the build we're
going to save that for the next episode
but what I will need to do is add some
windows in it only takes about a minute
for us to do this time as well for you
to see this time lapse but for me
building it it takes like 25 minutes and
I only did a slight amount of detailing
it's kind of interesting so you kind of
take for granted when you see time
lapses like this just how long they take
and then I've got to do all the camera
work afterwards it's just yeah time
consuming however I really do enjoy them
I really really do enjoy them and as for
the detailing I've got to say it's
fairly simple you add a few Windows here
or there you add a couple of trap doors
either side and then you add some plants
it's yeah I mean at this point I've
detailed so many of these windows it's
just second nature well it wasn't
exactly a long time lapse but we got not
what we needed to do done it is now full
of flowers and windows but you're
probably wondering what is my plan for
the next episode and I'm not gonna tell
you I'm really not going to tell you but
what I will say is that this is probably
the last time that it's going to look
like a really tall fantasy house
from some sort of novel it's just not
going to look like this after I've
finished in the next episode
I don't know whether what I'm going to
do is going to look good but soak it in
everybody because this is the last time
the house will definitely look like this
in fact I may even ask if I can take a
copy of this because I'm actually really
really proud of how this particular
build has come out I would rate this in
not one of my best or high quality
builds but one of my funnest builds it's
just really quirky and for some reason
it just works
it may look a little bit dull in
comparison to the giant plant that's
casting a spell
but it's mine and I'm rather attached to
it I really am and I'm gonna really
regret probably doing what I'm going to
do to this this poor wonderful house
that I've spent many an hour building
over time
but if scar is going to pull out a Vex
feather wand on me
well I'm gonna have to pull out the big
guns so
take it in
everything's about to change
thank you very much for watching and
good bye